[
{"question":"1. The execution of a loop typically starts with:",
"answers":{
            "a":"initialization statements",
            "b":"Loop body",
            "c":"test condition",
            "d":"update statements"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"2. The break statement is used to exit from:",
"answers":{
            "a":"an if statement",
            "b":"a for loop",
            "c":"a program",
            "d":"the main( ) function"
          },
"correctAnswer":"b"}, 

{"question":"3. A do-while loop is useful when we want that the statements within the loop must be executed",
"answers":{
            "a":"only once",
            "b":"At Least Once",
            "c":"More than once",
            "d":"None of the above"
          },
"correctAnswer":"b"},

{"question":"4. In what sequence the initialization, testing and execution of body is done in a do-while loop ",
"answers":{
            "a":"Initialization, execution of body, testing",
            "b":"Execution of body, initialization, testing",
            "c":"Initialization, testing, execution of body",
            "d":"None of the above"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"5. Which looping process checks the test condition at the end of the loop?",
"answers":{
            "a":"for",
            "b":"while",
            "c":"do-while",
            "d":"No looping peocess check condition at the end"
          },
"correctAnswer":"c"},

{"question":"6. A continue statement causes execution to skip to:",
"answers":{
            "a":"the end of the program",
            "b":"the first statement after the loop",
            "c":"the statement following the continue statement",
            "d":"the next iteration of the loop"
          },
"correctAnswer":"d"},

{"question":"7. The statement i++; is equivalent to:",
"answers":{
            "a":"i = i + i;",
            "b":"i = i + 1;",
            "c":"i = i - 1;",
            "d":"i - - ;"
          },
"correctAnswer":"b"},

{"question":"8. Another word for 'looping' is:",
"answers":{
            "a":"recapitulation ",
            "b":"tintinabulation ",
            "c":"iteration",
            "d":"reiteration"
          },
"correctAnswer":"c"},

{"question":"9. Which looping process is best used when the number of iterations is known?",
"answers":{
            "a":"for",
            "b":"while",
            "c":"do-while",
            "d":"all of the above"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"10.  Which of the following is not an infinite loop.",
"answers":{
            "a":"int i = 1 ; while ( 1 ) { i++ ; }",
            "b":"for( int i =1; i < 10 ; i--) printf('Hello World');",
            "c":"for(int i =1; i<100; i++) printf('Hello World');",
            "d":"int i = 0; do{ i-- printf('%d ',i); }while(i>0);"
          },
"correctAnswer":"c"}


]
